Decavoice
What's a Decavoice?
It's the genius behind Bombat's pellets.
Oh, my God.
You think he'll eat it?
You're supposed to draw butts.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I'm proud to announce that I've become a Bombat Ambassador.
As the first of the ambassadors.
I'm going to experience being a zookeeper at the Satsukiyama Zoo today!
And we have a very nice guest!
Please.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
I'm Kosugi from Black Manes.
Wombat hee-haw.
That's a big round of applause.
It's not a big round of applause, Yoza-chan.
It's just out of the blue.
I look like that wombat.
I don't know.
You're being too brief.
When we met...
We were on location for a movie together.
You were calling me Wombat, Wombat, Wombat.
I really like Wombat.
Look at my cell phone.
Wombat's Wombat Supporting Ambassador.
And...
It's on my cell phone.
No, that's funny, it's me.
And this one, too.
When we were eating after the location shoot...
I said, “Let's get a face like a wombat.
I thought it would end with him saying, “I'll use it as a standby screen.
But you did it!
Every day for more than half a year now.
I wake up looking at your face and go to bed looking at your face.I saw your face and I woke up and I saw your face and I went to bed.
That's crazy.
That's why I was so happy today.
So I'll tell you one more time.
There's a wombat in the zoo here in Satsukiya.
Kosugi told me to go see him.
Is this by any chance...
I noticed it.
A wombat!
He's wearing wombat ears.
Even Kosugi-san...
You can't do that!
You look scared.
Let's go in now.
You're already in before you know it, since it's free.
That's right. Anyone can come in.
Alpacas.
Ah!
They're feeding them.
He seems to be very good at it.
He's funny.
It's true.
Puddin'!
Hey, Puddin'.
Big eyes
Her eyes are so big and shiny!
Why are you going?
It says here that you're difficult!
Why did you hold out your hand?
Here he comes!
The wombat will be here soon.
Almost there, sir.
When he gets here...
First wombat!
Ah!
Oh!Ah!
Kokochan
Ah!
It came out.
It came out so much!
What do you think?
It came out at the perfect time.
It's really
It's so cute!
It's cute.
That's Mr. Wine.
Mr. Wine?
Yes.
He's 35 years old.
Is this Mr. Wine?
He's in the Guinness Book of Records for longevity.
He's really coming on!
I'm glad to see you're doing so well today.
Wow!
Wow, it's so soothing.
Kosugi-san looks like a wombat too.
Where does he do it?
He's so cute!
He said I look like him.
The one who looks like Kosugi is a boy named Fuku-kun.
I don't know if he's in the news yet.
If you like him so much...
Wine and Fuku-kun... and the way you look at them...
They look like...
Kosugi?
They're totally different.
From Yuchan's point of view.
Yes.
So we're going inside now.
What?What?
Don't you have a Wombat name to go with it?
Ours.
What's a wombat name?
Our wombat names.
This Wine.
Yuki-chan.
Yuki-chan
Fuku-kun
Like Ikkichi's Fuku-kun.
I see... a wombat name... what should we call him?
Since you're a wombat, you don't need YodaYukiKun anymore, do you?
That's right.
It doesn't matter if it is or isn't.
Something cute would be nice.
That's true.
But maybe he likes a name like “Fuku-kun”?
Fuku-kun's cute.
Hey...
If I had to pick just a name, I'd say wine.
Wine you think is cute?
White wine I think is cute.
White wine?
That's too much wine.
There was someone like this...
Beer.
Beer is too much beer.
Wine is still a cute name, but...
Beer Girl
Beer Girl.
What's your charm?
What is a charm point?
How do you use it for all kinds of customers?
Mine?
I'm often told that my voice is loud and audible.
They say they can tell whose voice it is. People say they know whose voice it is.
The big voice.
What's a “big voice”?
What's one-button name Decavoice?
It's too funny.
Let's start with the big voice.
Davey.
Oh, my God, you're like fat.
Oh, come on.
“Devo” almost sounds like a fat guy.
That's not what I meant.
Call me Davey.
You can't say “Davey”.
Pronunciation is important.
It's pronounced “day-na”!
Katakana “day” and “bo” and “dae-bo”.
Day-boo.
And Bee-chan.
Bee-chan.
Great.
Okay, today we're going to send you Daebo and Bee-chan.
You're going to send them home?
Let's go, Devoe.
Let's go, Bee.
Okay.
Shouldn't it be Mr. Bebo or something?
Oh, yeah.
I'll be your new keeper.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Pleasure to meet you.
You're in charge? In charge of the main office?
Yes, I'll be in charge of the main office.
Please guide me as I am.
My name is Endo.
En-chan
En-chan, En-chan
I'm En-chan, Enchan-sensei.
What do you want me to do first?What do you want me to do first?
I'm gonna wash my hands.
I'll wash my hands.
That's what I'm usually instructed to do.
Hands first.
I never thought I'd see the day I'd be here washing my hands.
It's true. Today is a historic day.
It's all about the food, isn't it?
Wow.
Oh, that looks delicious.
Looks delicious.
Let's start with the sweet potatoes.
Yes, sir.
Cut it into pieces and eat it!
350 grams, right?
Yes, sir.
I'll have you measure it for me.
It's so tiny!
Two millimeters.
That's about right, but...
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go to B-chan.
Here we go, B-chan.
Let's start with this one.
Okay, please take a look at this.
About this much?
You might want to cut as much as you can.
Like this.
Thin skin, dry, but just a little bit.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Cut it.
It's a little short.
Continue this way.
What? What?
500... no, 300...
How much? Can I chew?
Hmm?
I have to cut here, too.
That's good.
Like this?
Oh, it's about 260!
Still 350?
Are we missing another 100 or so?
Is that about right?
Yeah. - Okay.
All right.
Oh, hey.
A little bit.
A little bit of a week.
I'm gonna have to ask you to pull a little week.
Tiny Week.
Ooh.
Wow.
Is that on there?
Here.
Like this, like this!
That's amazing!
You're a wombat potato genius!
I'm a wombat potato genius.
You never bothered to say that.
Now I had to say it all.
It's hard to get in here, isn't it?
I'll take that part.
Are you sure you're okay?
You're not gonna hang up?
No, don't pretend. Don't do that.
You don't know the answer to that. Don't pretend.
Please don't hang up.
No, I won't hang up. I really won't hang up.
Mr. Baybo.
I'm not going to cut off your finger, Mr. Baybo.I don't have the guts to cut off Mr. Baybo's finger.
I can't broadcast that.
I'll keep it under wraps, just in case.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wow, you're good!
Dave Cooking.
Dave Cooking, are you okay if I don't hear you? Right now.
Dave cooking.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It sounds like “Dave cooking.
Dave cooking.
No, I already said Dave cooking.
But you're good.
Oh, you're getting used to it.
I'm getting used to it.
So this is what you're going to put in your stomach, Fuku-kun?
I'm so happy.
After all this time, I thought it suddenly looked like a slice.
I thought it looked like a takikomi gohan potato.
That's what you said.
I'm supposed to be like this and I don't even notice it.
I don't know why.
When I noticed it, it turned out like this.
It looks like a takikomi gohan potato.
I don't know how it came to be like this.
It's like a mark, like a wai-wai mark...
I'm sure it's like this...
Chopsticks, right there!
Gums!
That's funny.
Why does it move like that?
Is it the hand?
I can't get nutrients with this.
I've seen this before.
It cost you 20 grams.
20 grams.
I'll give you a perfect challenge.
That's right.Yes, you're right.
If I get this right.
I'll be a wombat.
Who decides if you get it right, you'll be a wombat?
I don't know if I can be a wombat or not.
20 grams.
Oh, if I can get it to 70...
Oh, yeah, yeah, 20.
Ten.
That's not even close.
I'm such a glutton.
I've been told 20, but I'm already at 35.
I'm over 35.
I eat too much.
I don't know... I guess that's about right.
What?
Like 70.
That's a bit much.
We should talk to him.
I'll go.
Oh, oh, oh, you just dropped that in there.
Whoa! Wait a minute!
You're a wombat pellet genius!
Oh, it fits!
I mean, you're a wombat rice weight genius!
Seriously? Oh, just...
It's perfect!
Yes!
What kind of talent is that?
Where are you going to put it to use?
I think I'm going to get a job.
I don't think it's time for dinner right now.
I can't fry what I just made.
He's going to eat it later.
So...
It's tiny.
Can you fry them?
Like the chives?Like the chives you just saw?
Just in time for a snack.
Here.
I can fry this.
Like potherb mustard.
You.
That's good.
I'm here!
It's going up.
Oh, my God!
There he is.
Oh, my goodness.
That's him?
Good boy.
Hey, mister!
Dinner's ready.
Come here, boy.
At the snack bar, Fukko-kun.
At the snack bar.
It's just the two of us.
They're here! Here they come!
Gung, long time no see.
Open it again.
Oh!
Why are you covered in sand like that?
Try a little.
I knew it when I saw the fukufuku.
The way the temperature rises is totally different.
I'm going to throw up.
Such dull eyes, aren't they?
Finally, two shots!
Two shots!
Nice to meet you, Fuk Fuk Fuk!
I've heard a lot about you.
He's staring at me so intently.
Here you go.
Fuk Fuk Fuk.Blah, blah, blah.
He ate it with his eyes closed.
He's so cute.
I hope it's good.
Hey, DeBeau.
Don't call me that.
Oh, my eyes are closed. My eyes are closed.
You're cute.
He's cute. That's for sure.
Aren't you hooked?
You know what? Your face is totally different.
This is the face I saw when I met Fuku-kun.
Really? How does he look?
Is he getting closer to Monbat?
No, it's a good look.
You want some, asshole?
Why do I have to eat like Fuku-kun now?
Is it good?
What?
I'm sure there's nothing wrong with it.
What are you doing?
It's bitter.
It doesn't taste good.
Hmm?
Mr. Tsuboro did the same thing.
What did it taste like?
Elementary school.
Is that right?
I ate it in elementary school.
Is it good?
ạo Goski.
Bitter and fibrous.
When I was in elementary school, I used to gather the grass and roast it with a stone.
I used to give it to my little brother.
Eat it yourself.
Why do you roast it and give it to your little brother?
It's good for you.They say it's good for you.
What should I do next, senpai?
Next, we'll clean up Fukuko's room.
Fukko-kun, please leave once.
He's getting ready for bed.
You're like a keeper when it comes to cleaning rooms.
That's right.
He looks like he wants to get out.
I want to get out.
Look how cute he is.
Look at him. He's got mud on his head like that.
This is so cute.
Look at his back.
Here we go.
I opened it myself.
Bye-bye!
He's going on his own.
Nice back.
That was cool.
There's a toilet around here.
The rest of Mr. Koshik's stuff is down.
Womblake?
Combat poo... it's square.
What?
Why do you think?
His poop is square?
Yes, sir.
Quiz.
If it's square...
It's like a vending machine in a card game.
Like a receipt that comes out in a straight bar
It's a three-dimensional square.
A three-dimensional square.
Her asshole is not a rectangle.
It's not.
It's actually poo.
I'm making a live lining.I'm making a live line.
So that the wind won't blow it away.
He says, “This is my place.
This is my place, and I show it with my poop.
It's square so it won't be blown away.
It's shaped like a square, but it comes out square?
It comes out square.
What's going on? It's built in.
I'm not.
Don't tell me it's round.
I'm just like everyone else.
That's...
Why am I so square like a wombat?
I don't need territory.
I just thought maybe...
Why don't you just leave me on my own turf at the corner of the house?
I'm going to have to ask you to switch targets.
I see.
I got it.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Is it open?
I can't hold it any longer.
Just a little bit.
Come on, come on.
Yes, sir.
You guessed it... on the video the other day.
Hey.
Business events. You sleep here.
When do you use the hole?
At night, I come in.
Outside.
Oh.
But you didn't tell me I was your favorite sound bat.
I don't know how you feel about that.
Yeah, I just fixed it...
What are you doing?
I'm just trying to fix it.You just need to fix it.
It's beautiful now.
That's a lot of work, Mr. Keeper.
You're going to have to do this a lot... and feed him twice a day.
This is the bed.
This is where they sleep.
This is where you put the flooring.
Where?
The flooring?
I'll leave the dormitory to the books.
This is where you'll sleep tonight, on the bed you made.
My guess is that she'll sleep on the bed I made.
I'm so happy.
Is this good?
It's a little like a sweet potato.
You've already tasted it.
What are you gonna do when you get to the next stage with grass stuck in your teeth?
That's possible.
Do you need a pillow or something?
This one's your head, I'm on the other side.
My bed's on this side.
Pillow's good.
That's a nice pillow, let's go a little bit further.
Is your head against the wall?
Yeah, I'm facing this way.
Yeah, okay.
I'm with you.
My head's on the wall.
I'm glad you're here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
That's good.
Well, you can see how hard it is to get a little bit of experience.
It's true.
Now that you've had a chance to experience being a keeper...
Did you like it? Wombat.
Well, to tell you the truth, I liked it.Well, to be frank, I'm starting to like you.
Yes, I do.
After all, taking care of them and seeing them up close like this.
and having Mi-chan tell me what's good and what's cute about wombats, I fell in love with them.
So you've come to like them.
Yes.
Do you want to be a wombat now?
What do you mean?
When you like a wombat, you want to be one.
No, I can.
You can?
You can be a wombat, Mr. Devoe.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
I don't know what that means at this point, but I'll be there.
I almost did once.
But then my human heart came out and I felt embarrassed.
Of course, you're human.
I think the two of us can do it with Mr. Devoe.
Let's do it.
Wow, it's a beautiful day.
It's a beautiful day.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's a beautiful day, Hebekun.
Bee, it's a beautiful day.
Bee-chan! What do you mean?
Flowers are blooming. Aren't they beautiful?
You're turning into a grandfather.
I wonder if they're good. You're not supposed to eat them.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Bee.
Here, here, here. Scratch your bum here.
I don't think that's a good idea, Bee.
I don't think you should be scratching your butt like a warmat.
You want to try? No?
Okay. Oh, I'm looking.Okay. Oh, I'm looking.
I'm looking at it.
You're looking at it.
Now?
Fuku-kun.
He said he has more friends.
What are they always doing in our place?
Mr. Fuku.
Thank you for taking care of me and my new friend B.
B-chan.
Deb.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for taking care of me and Deb.
No, no, no.
Not so territorial.
That feels good. Oh, my God, that feels good.
It feels so good. It feels so good. It's so different when it's just the two of you.
I didn't even last 30 seconds in there. I mean, I do a lot of things for a long time, but...
I've never done anything like this before. How do you like it?
But when I got down to it and became a wombat...
I think I could taste it. I think so.
I think this life might be good.
That's so sweet of the zookeeper to cut you a meal.
It's a little embarrassing to be watched over so closely.
Wombats should react to humans when they do things.
That's true. I want them to say, “Oh!” or something.
From now on, when you see him, you should say “Ooh” when he does something.
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, it's so warm.
What's this?
Yay!
I saw that.
Second time you've seen me on youtube.
It's pretty heavy, just like wombats.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It stings!It stings!
Wombat ice cream is the best after a hard day's work!
Wait a minute, it's so good!
I don't mean that in a bad way.
It's just not on the scale of this animal.
I mean that in a good way.
How was it? Wombat ice cream.
Ice cream? I don't think it's ice cream.
It's not just Wombat Ice Cream Cloud, it's the big ending.
It's the big ending, right here.
How was it?
It was great.
Yoda told me about the Wombats.
And now that I'm here...
I thought they were really cute.
I fell in love with wombats.
and I like you even more.
Thank you very much.
You're really charming.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you liked it.
It was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much for today.
It was great.
Please come again.
Please subscribe and rate our channel!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for watching!